[Applause]
[Music]
good evening and welcome to the 84th
annual Academy
Awards I'm your host Daniel Tosh you may
know me from such films as The Love Guru
and that's
it sorry if I don't hit all my marks
tonight uh Brett Ratner told me
rehearsals are for
homosexuals Eddie Murphy couldn't be
here because he's busy getting blown by
a transgender
prostitute I'd like to thank George
Clooney for taking a break from screwing
every cocktail waitress in town to be
here tonight the academy must be honored
let me smell your finger George no
woman's ever good enough for you but
apparently the script for The Men Who
Stare at Goats was nice to see Merill
stre
yes she is one of the great acting
talents of our time just imagine what
she could have accomplished if she were
pleasant to look at I tease you were
looking as gorgeous as you can at this
point in your
life what's nominated tonight Jay Edgar
who would have guessed a movie about the
head of the FBI set in the 30s would
have been boring my favorite part was
when the lady sitting in the road behind
me made a phone call you're 81 Clen
Eastwood the only thing you should be
directing is your nurse to give you
another Spoonful Of Applesauce whose
idea was it to cast leard DiCaprio as a
fat bald old man he looks like a
14-year-old boy I feel like I'm
committing a crime when I'm masturbating
to him and now a song
thear